bills.com 2014-06-21

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: January 1, 2014_

This privacy policy applies to the following Web sites: [http://www.theeasyloansite.com](http://www.theeasyloansite.com/), [http://www.lendage.com](http://www.lendage.com/), and Bills.com.

Bills.com, LLC (Bills.com) recognizes your expectation of privacy and security and we greatly respect your privacy concerns. This Privacy Policy describes how we gather information, what we do with the information we collect and what steps we take to safeguard your privacy and protect your personal information.

To ensure that this Privacy Policy is up-to-date and responsive to changes in our website(s), our business activities, relevant laws and regulations and developments in the applicable technology we reserve the right to change and/or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Your use of our website(s) constitutes your consent to the current version of our Privacy Policy.

Bills.com participates in the Council of Better Business Bureaus' BBBOnLine® Reliability Program. Participation in this program is limited to those willing to commit to the program's strict information use restrictions and periodic review by BBBOnLine of our information use and security practices. In addition, Bills.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [customercare@bills.com](mailto:customercare@bills.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe complaint page](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

We have organized this Privacy Policy as a series of answers to questions that we have found to be of most interest to consumers. If you do not see the answer to any question you may have about what information we collect, how we collect information and what we do with the information we collect, please contact us at the following address:

If by e-mail: [customercare@bills.com](mailto:customercare@bills.com)

If in writing:  
Bills.com  
1875 South Grant Street, Suite 500  
San Mateo, CA 94402

###  What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This privacy policy covers several websites Bills.com owns and operates, including www.bills.com, [www.lendage.com](http://www.lendage.com/) and [www.theeasyloansite.com](http://www.theeasyloansite.com/). We may, from time to time, add additional websites and/or domains to our portfolio. Whether or not any particular site is specifically identified in this Privacy Policy, this Privacy Policy applies to any website owned and/or operated by Bills.com. The TRUSTe privacy program covers the sites www.bills.com, [www.lendage.com](http://www.lendage.com/) and [www.theeasyloansite.com](http://www.theeasyloansite.com/).

This Privacy Policy covers what we do with any personal information you may submit or authorize us to obtain, as well as any other information that we may gather when you access any of our websites. This Privacy Policy also covers any of your personal and other information that any of our business partners may share with us.

Please note that our policies and procedures apply only to websites owned and/or operated by us and not to websites maintained by other companies or to any website to which we may link or to unrelated businesses with which we may share information.

###  What is Personal Information?

Personal information is any information that you provide to us or authorize us to obtain that identifies you, personally, or that can be logically associated with you. Examples of personal information that will be collected on some of our sites include your name, your address, your e-mail address and your Social Security Number. Demographic information such as gender, age, zip code, etc. is generally not considered personal information.

###  Why Do You Need To Collect My Personal Information?

We collect and use personal information in order to respond more completely to your requests for products and services offered through our websites and those of our business partners. We also collect personal and other information in order to make you aware of products and/or services that are likely to be of interest to you.

###  What Personal and Other Information Do You Collect and/or Maintain?

We collect and maintain the information you provide to us whenever you visit our website(s), such as:

  * Any information you provide to us when you request a product or service. This information may include your name, your address, your telephone number and in some cases your Social Security Number. Depending upon the product or service you request, you may also be asked to provide additional information such as the amount of your current unsecured debt and the identity of your creditors, information about your mortgage and other financial and personal information.
  * Any information you provide to us or to one of our business partners when you request a quote or a product or service offered by or through one of our websites.
  * Information, such as your e-mail address, that you provide to us when you register to receive communications from us or when you communicate with us through our customer service facility, or otherwise correspond with us.

We also collect other, non-personal information, which is broadly defined as any information that is not and cannot be directly associated with you. An example of this type of non-personal information would be your zip code.

In addition to the information we collect from you, we may also receive information about you from other on-line or off-line sources. For example, if you provide us with personal information along with an appropriate authorization we may request and obtain a credit report and credit score.

###  How Do You Use The Personal and Other Information You Collect?

We use the personal information you supply to us, or that you authorize us to obtain, to provide to you the service(s) or product(s) that you request. We may also use your personal and other information to enhance your experience on our website(s) by displaying content based on your preferences and/or to send information to you about additional products or services in which you may be interested. We may “depersonalize” your personal information to enable us to use that information, aggregated with the information of others, for research, analysis and modeling purposes.

###  With Whom Do You Share My Information?

If you submit a request for a product or service, we will share the personal and other information you supply (such as your name, email, zip code, loan amounts etc) with those product and service providers that have agreed to participate in our network. Generally, these product and service providers, such as mortgage lenders, credit agencies and debt relief providers, are prohibited from using the information we provide to them for any other purpose, including using your information for other, unrelated marketing purposes. Note that we do not share your social security number with anyone, apart from credit agencies for the purpose of obtaining your credit report when specifically requested to do so by you.

By submitting your request you are consenting to being contacted by us or by our business partners, through any means, based on the information you provide to us, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state Do Not Call List or the Do Not Call List of any specific institution. If, after you are contacted by that product or service provider, you do not wish to be contacted by that person again you must make a specific request to the product or service provider, not to Bills.com.

We may also share your personal and other information with a third-party that provides a service or supplies a specific functionality to us, such as a call center operator. These service providers will be provided only with the information necessary for them to perform their functions and are not allowed to share any of the provided information with others for any purpose whatsoever.

Any person with whom we share your personal information is also required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations and will have its own privacy policies that should be made available to you at the time you are first contacted.

###  Are There Any Other Circumstances Where You Disclose My Information?

We may be required to share your information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders or other forms of legal process. We may elect to share information when, in our reasonable judgment, such sharing is necessary or appropriate for the investigation or prevention of illegal activities, including actual or suspected fraud, real or potential threats to the physical safety of any person or otherwise as required by law.

In addition, if we are merged with, or acquired by, another company the successor company will have access to all of the information collected and maintained by us. In such a circumstance, the successor company would continue to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

###  How Do You Collect Information?

We collect certain types of non-personal information and technical data from each visitor to our website(s). For example, when you click on a banner advertisement or text link that is associated with one of our websites, the banner or text placement, along with the time of your visit, your Internet Protocol address and other path-related information, is sent to us. Similarly, the page requests you make when you visit our website(s) are stored and used by us. We use this information, none of which is or can be personally associated with you, for statistical and analytic purposes, to help us understand which page views are most appealing to our customers and to help us improve the likelihood that we will be able to offer you only products or services in which you have a genuine interest.

  * **What Are Cookies?** “Cookies” are small files that are placed automatically on your computer system when you visit a website. Cookies enable a website to recognize you as a return visitor and, by keeping track of your website activity, help us identify which pages to serve to you while reducing the time it takes for those pages to load. Cookies enable us to personalize and enrich your experience and are not tied in any way to your personal information. If you do not wish to accept cookies or if you wish to remove cookies that remain in your browser following the close of your browser session, you may adjust the settings on your web browser to prevent cookies from being placed on your hard drive. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings.
  * **Do You Use Any Other Advertising Technology?** We use third-party advertising technology to serve ads on our website(s) and on the websites where we advertise. Generally, advertisements are served by ad networks, such as DoubleClick, that are independent of us. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [TRUSTe’s privacy page](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
  * **What Are Web Beacons?** We, and our third party advertising partners, employ a software technology called Web Beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons are, like cookies, small files that enable an ad server to recognize a visitor’s cookie when the visitor returns to a particular site. Web beacons are also used in e-mail advertising to help track which e-mail messages have been opened. Web beacons are used to track the movement of visitors to our sites and, like cookies, are not tied to any personal information.
  * **Do You Follow Do-Not-Track Signals?** Because an industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established, our information collection practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy regardless of any “Do Not Track” signals that may be sent by certain browsers or selected by you.

###  How Do You Safeguard The Information You Collect?

The security of your personal information is a very high priority for us and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. Some of the measures we take are:

  * Limiting access to personal information to those employees who are critical to the delivery of products and services to you.
  * Implementing appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to guard against unauthorized access or use.
  * Requiring appropriate consents and protections from our business partners before we share any personal information.

Bills.com and its affiliates use commercially reasonable physical and technical security measures to protect all personal information in our possession. Sensitive information such as social security numbers are encrypted using secure sockets layer encryption (SSL) from the time of your submission and while it is stored by us. We cannot, however, guarantee or warrant the absolute security of any system or that any information we hold will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

Third party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to this website. No personal information is collected by these cookies. You can opt out of third party vendor’s cookies at any time by visiting this page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

###  How Long Do You Retain My Personal Information?

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Non-personal information may be retained indefinitely.

Under certain circumstances, Federal and/or state law may require us to retain your personal information for different periods of time. Accordingly, we may not be able to delete or otherwise remove your personal information from our systems.

###  Can I Correct or Remove My Personal Information?

If you believe there are factual errors in any of the information you have submitted through one of our websites, please contact us and advise us of the error. To protect your privacy and security we may require that you verify your identity before we make any requested changes to personal information.

###  What Choices Do I Have?

You can elect not to provide personal information to us, although if you do not complete and submit the information we ask for we may not be able to provide you with the most complete responses or you may not be able to access all the available features.

If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [customercare@bills.com](mailto:customercare@bills.com). If you decide, at a later point in time, that you no longer want us to share your personal information with our business partners you may notify us either by sending us an e-mail or by writing to us at the following address:

1875 South Grant Street  
Suite 500  
San Mateo, CA 94402

###  Do You Use My Personal Information to Contact Me Without Permission?

We do not send unsolicited messages. To receive our newsletter via e-mail you must sign up on one of our websites. If you decide at a later time that you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may unsubscribe using the “unsubscribe” link on each newsletter that you receive. If you have any problems unsubscribing, please contact us immediately at [customercare@bills.com](mailto:customercare@bills.com).

Bills.com has a strict “anti-spam” policy. You will not receive Bills.com e-mails unless you submit your e-mail address to us or register on one of our websites to receive communications. We do not permit any third-party e-mail service to send unsolicited e-mails — spam — to any person who has not previously given their permission to receive such communications to that third party e-mail service. If you wish to stop receiving future e-mails from a third-party e-mail service, we recommend you follow the opt-out instructions included in the e-mail. An “unsubscribe” link should appear within or at the top or bottom of any e-mail you receive.

###  Testimonials

If you submit a testimonial to us, we will ask for your permission to post your testimonial prior to any public use. We will post your name as given to us in your testimonial. We may post a photo of you or use a stock photo. Please be aware that any personal information you submit as a testimonial to be posted can be read, collected, or used by the general public, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to include in any testimonial you choose to submit. If at any time you decide to remove your testimonial, please contact us via e-mail or postal mail.

###  Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button (and Widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###  Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and e-mail address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

###  A Special Note about Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect, use or share personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the products and/or services offered on our website(s) only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

###  Special Notification for California Residents

California residents who provide us with their personal information may request certain information regarding disclosures made to third parties for direct marketing purposes, including the names and address of those to whom such disclosures have been made. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following mailing address: California Privacy Request, Bills.com, 1875 South Grant Street, Suite 500, San Mateo, CA 94402. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year.
